All right, so Jubilee has clipped a
piece of the debate between myself,
Amanda Seals, and other black
conservatives. This was about
reparations. Now, I was not able to get
my answer out. I'll explain why, but
first, let's check this out. How long
are we going to sit here focusing on
trying to get reparations? It's been how
many years since slavery? 150 years,
1865.
Whenever there's a real thing that this
country wants to do, they do it.
>> Okay. Um, well, first I'll start with it
will help on even just a moral level.
The reality is that the United States
has become very comfortable with the
fact that it does not consider black
people equal. And it shows that in many
ways that well that I'm sure we will
discuss over the course of today. But
ultimately, there has not been a
committed concerted effort to shifting
the mindset around the use of black
people as a labor force in this nation.
Back when it was slavery, now in the
voice in the use of slavery as slave
labor in prisons. So on a basic cultural
level, reparations are an act of repair.
They are an effort to say our bet, we
see you now. We have seen that done with
Japanese folks who were put in
internment camps. We have seen that done
with Jewish folks. We have seen that
done even in the case of slave owners
who received reparations. When it comes
to the use of tax dollars to pay
reparations, and this is going to come
up a lot today, it's a matter of values,
right? For me, my value system
circulates around the fact that I think
that as a community, we should all be
engaged in repair for our community. So,
I don't think there should be any
problem with there being tax dollars
spent at repairing consistent efforts
that have been made to impede black
people.
>> All right, there's a lot there. First of
all, I was able to answer this during
the time when I was in front of her, but
my answer got cut off because I was
trying to say that, hey, we vote in the
black community 93% for the Democratic
Party. There's no incentive to do
anything. Listen, it's a carrot they
dangle in front of us and they never
ever ever ever do it. Whenever there's
an issue in this country that they
really want to accomplish, they do it.
Remember the stop Asian hate situation?
There was a problem. There was a bill
drafted and then it was a law. Every
other thing they really want to do, they
get done. Reparations is obviously not
one of them. You had Barack Obama for
not one term but two consecutive terms
and it was never even the question for
his administration to do anything that
even got close to that. If you have him
in office and nothing happens, what
makes you think anything will happen?
But beyond that, I don't even care if it
does or if it doesn't. At the end of the
day, I'm going to keep living my life.
I'm not worried about mythological white
man coming down from the sky like Jesus
to save me. I and many guys like me from
the hood, black Americans, real black
Americans with both sides of my family
going all the way back to the boat in
Virginia 1600s. Okay, we don't care
about stuff like that. We go out here,
we get money, we make things happen with
no excuses.